[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FactionIntro_Covenant_01",
        "Type": "FactionStory_Covenant",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "FactionIntro_Covenant_01_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9801_Florina_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FactionIntro_Covenant_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 17,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "FactionIntro_Covenant_01_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": null,
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Hope and Service",
        "Description": "Covenant Initiation Quest: Florina has requested you aid Feldan save what you can at Olcott Farm and then meet her at the Church in Everfall.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What do you need help with?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "It's painful to admit, but when the Olcott farm fell to the Lost, I offered to help them reclaim their valuables. \\n\\nI came here with the old man, Felden Olcott, but the Withered are too many. I had no choice but to run.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Please, convince old man Olcott to leave. \\n\\nIf I don't get him back to town safely... well, I couldn't bear it.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "So you made it out of the farm with your soul intact? And I suppose you reclaimed the Olcotts' keepsakes as well? \\n\\nI am ashamed - you kept faith and came through, where I failed. Perhaps I am not Covenant material.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FactionIntro_Covenant_Vector_01",
        "Type": "FactionStory_Covenant",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "FactionIntro_Covenant_Vector_01_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9802_Lethold",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FactionIntro_Covenant_Vector_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FactionIntro_Covenant_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 17,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "FactionIntro_Covenant_Vector_01_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": null,
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Covenant Enclave",
        "Description": "Covenant Initiation Quest: Florina has asked you to visit her brother Lethold at the Covenant enclave in south-eastern Everfall. She has attuned your spirit with the shrine, so you may travel there safely.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I can do that. What's the message?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Thank you. Lethold undoubtedly worries for my welfare, so please reassure him. \\n\\nI committed to helping people here in Oxboro for my Covenant initiation, and there's more to be done. Hopefully, I'll see you both at the enclave soon.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I really do suggest you inquire about becoming a Covenant Initiate yourself. \\n\\nOn Aeternum, it's critical one finds a higher purpose to serve.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Please, good visitor, tell me, have you come from Oxboro? \\n\\nMy dear sister Florina embarked on a quest there some time ago, and I am anxious to hear word of her welfare.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FactionIntro_Covenant_02",
        "Type": "FactionStory_Covenant",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 19,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "FactionIntro_Covenant_02_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9802_Lethold",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FactionIntro_Covenant_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FactionIntro_Covenant_Vector_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 17,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "FactionIntro_Covenant_02_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": null,
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Justice and Courage",
        "Description": "Covenant Initiation Quest: Lethold beseeches you to rush to Clearview Crypt to end whatever terrible acts are transpiring, save Templar Damiano, and return to him at the Covenant Enclave.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What happened to the Initiates?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Their cowardice has very likely led them to a dark fate, though it is neither surprising nor unjust. \\n\\nIt appears that in their mad flight, they sought refuge in Clearview Crypt, which has now become disturbingly quiet.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I must consult with Lumen Morellus about this alleged heresy. \\n\\nI hope you find Damiano, and the Initiates as well. I pray they are still whole.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "The fortitude of Templar Damiano is proven by his safe return, though it is your courage that saved him. \\n\\nIt sounds like justice was served with the Initiates. But I wonder, how did they succumb to become Corrupted?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FactionIntro_Covenant_Vector_02",
        "Type": "FactionStory_Covenant",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "FactionIntro_Covenant_Vector_02_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9803_Morellus",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FactionIntro_Covenant_Vector_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FactionIntro_Covenant_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 17,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "FactionIntro_Covenant_Vector_02_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": null,
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Lumen's Words",
        "Description": "Covenant Initiation Quest: Adjudicator Lethold has asked you to speak with Lumen Morellus at the Covenant Enclave for your final initiation test.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I will listen carefully.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Very well. I must attend to cleansing the foul presence of those Initiates from our sacred halls. \\n\\nWhen Florina returns, I hope all this is far behind us.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I suggest you speak with the Lumen soon. \\n\\nThere is no reason to delay.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Thank you for giving me this chance to express my gratitude for the rescue of Templar Damiano. \\n\\nI see in your eyes the light of a great potential. You would shine as a member of our order, and bring inspiration to many struggling souls.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FactionIntro_Covenant_03",
        "Type": "FactionStory_Covenant",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 21,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "FactionIntro_Covenant_03_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9803_Morellus",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FactionIntro_Covenant_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FactionIntro_Covenant_Vector_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 17,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "FactionIntro_Covenant_03_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": null,
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Inspiration and Redemption",
        "Description": "Covenant Initiation Quest: Morellus has enlisted you to lure the Corrupted Templar back to Nettlerest Graveyard, best him in battle, collect his cursed necklace, and return to the Convenant Enclave.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I can be trusted in such things.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I expected as much. The problem I need help with is related to Templar Titus Invectus, the one who oversaw the training of our fallen Initiates. \\n\\nI'm afraid this has driven Titus quite mad, and he, too, is now Corrupted, but through no fault of his own.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I strongly suggest you do not attempt to use the relic. \\n\\nIt is an insidious poison, Corruption.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "There, now we can safely say this whole sordid affair is concluded with some measure of redemption. \\n\\nLethold is a champion of righteousness and justice, and a strong leader.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FactionIntro_Covenant_Recruitment",
        "Type": "FactionStory_Covenant",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "FactionIntro_Covenant_Recruitment_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FactionIntro_Covenant_Recruitment",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FactionIntro_Covenant_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 17,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "FactionIntro_Covenant_Recruitment_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9806_C_0001_RankUp",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": true,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Committing to the Cause",
        "Description": "Covenant Recruitment: You can now join the Covenant.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Alright. Where do I sign up?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I am thrilled to hear you affirm your interest. The Covenant will shine brighter with you standing in our ranks. \\n\\nGo and speak to Lumen Beyza. I have already vouched for your worthiness. And hope be with you… always.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Take your time, this is not a decision to be made lightly.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "N/A",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FactionIntro_Marauders_01",
        "Type": "FactionStory_Marauders",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "FactionIntro_Marauders_01_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9805_Tibbs_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FactionIntro_Marauders_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 17,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "FactionIntro_Marauders_01_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": null,
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": " A First Step of Many",
        "Description": "Marauder Initiation Quest: Lieutenant Tibbs wants you to collect Lost Ears and a Knight's Signet ring at Lugdunum Fields for some sort of magic and then meet him at the ruin steps to the North of the farm.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"All right, you've got my attention.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "That’s the spirit! Northwest's a fort filled with unbelievable wonders. Need odd things to get inside. Magic, you see. Ears from the soulless Lost, a ring from a knight. \\n\\nGrab that lot from Lugdunum Fields, and meet me there.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Oi! Won’t get far loitering around here with these louts! Look, you get them ears, and I promise, I’ll show you something special, sure as my name's Tibbs. \\n\\nYou know what they all say! Always trust a Tibbs!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Don’t give me that look, this place is FULL of wonders! Look at me, looking at you, eh! \\n\\nThe Marauders are my kind of soldiers, see. Family now. And I think you should join our crew. Now, how about another tip from Tibbs?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FactionIntro_Marauders_02",
        "Type": "FactionStory_Marauders",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 19,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "FactionIntro_Marauders_02_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9805_Tibbs_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FactionIntro_Marauders_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FactionIntro_Marauders_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 17,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "FactionIntro_Marauders_02_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": null,
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Fortune Favors",
        "Description": "Marauder Initiation Quest: Lieutenant Tibbs has directed you to thrash some pirates and steal some black powder barrels at the Pirate Stockpile and then return to the Marauders Enclave.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Say ears one more time…\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Oi, no, no! Though it is Lost again. Pirates round here, always a pain in our side. \\n\\nTracked some of them down yesterday. Northeast, hiding like rats. Fight ’em, plunder ’em, burn their claim, and take their boom.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Those powder barrels, aye? We’ll be using those to impress Strou'dahia in the next step of our little plan. \\n\\nThe rest of the ruckus should let them know we mean business. Crash into that cave and plunder away!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Oh ho! Someone's got a mess of booty! Hope you gave those blackguards a good walloping. \\n\\nHow’s the prize? Ten percent for me then, eh? Fee, tax, and all.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FactionIntro_Marauders_Vector",
        "Type": "FactionStory_Marauders",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "FactionIntro_Marauders_Vector_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9806_Stroudahia_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FactionIntro_Marauders_Vector",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FactionIntro_Marauders_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 17,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "FactionIntro_Marauders_Vector_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": null,
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Threshold Guardian",
        "Description": "Marauder Initiation Quest: Lieutenant Tibbs has asked you to speak with Gladiator Strou'dahia at the Marauder Enclave for your final initiation test.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Sounds like my kind of test.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Oh ho! There it is! Those bombs ain't the only things with spark! \\n\\nNow, go talk to Gladiator Strou'dahia, and show the Marauders what you've got!",
        "InProgressResponse": "Off you trot, mate. Talk to the Doctore and I'll await your return.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Good, stand before me. You have fought boldly so far. Should you wish to join our ranks I have one final test of strength and skill. \\n\\nIt is time. Let us begin.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FactionIntro_Marauders_03",
        "Type": "FactionStory_Marauders",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 21,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "FactionIntro_Marauders_03_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9806_Stroudahia_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FactionIntro_Marauders_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FactionIntro_Marauders_Vector",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 17,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "FactionIntro_Marauders_03_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": null,
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Broken Bones and Blasted Bulwarks",
        "Description": "Marauder Initiation Quest: Gladiator Stroudahia has ordered you to best Varangians and rescue captives at Stonereach Keep. You must also complete Tibb's secret mission, before returning to the Marauders' Enclave",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I would fight for glory.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The Varangians have begun to take some of our members prisoner. No Marauder lets their brethren stay in chains. \\n\\nFree the imprisoned recruits who were less fortunate, and take the Varangian Knights down a peg. Make them feel our wrath!",
        "InProgressResponse": "Were it you in captivity, you would hope for a quicker rescue? Suffering festers through inaction. \\n\\nMove with purpose, and guide your steel relentlessly towards your goals.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Those who would risk themselves to save their comrades are always welcome in the Marauders. \\n\\nWe always stand together, always look after our own. Now, I know I can trust you in battle.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FactionIntro_Marauders_Recruitment",
        "Type": "FactionStory_Marauders",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "FactionIntro_Marauders_Recruitment_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FactionIntro_Marauders_Recruitment",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FactionIntro_Marauders_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 17,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "FactionIntro_Marauders_Recruitment_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9806_M_0001_RankUp",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": true,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "One of Us",
        "Description": "Marauders Recruitment Quest: You can now join the Marauders.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Alright. Where would I enlist?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "This is good to hear. I would be honored to fight beside you in the battles ahead. \\n\\nI've already spoken with Smiggs. Go to him and he will enter you into our charters.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Go to Smiggs with haste. Tonight, we feast!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "n/a",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_01",
        "Type": "FactionStory_Syndicate",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_01_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9807_Aventus_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 17,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_01_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": null,
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Fickle Fusions, Fanged Folly",
        "Description": "Syndicate Initiation Quest: Aventus has hired you to lure the altered wolves to Midnight Den and cull them, then meet him at the Syndicate Enclave to the north-east when you are finished.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You offer knowledge?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, and the most valuable kind, indeed, if you assist! \\n\\nYou see, I've been testing alchemical lures on the local wolves. Results were promising, until one of the wolves consumed the bait... and grew in both size and ferocity.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Do not feel too sorry for the wolves. \\n\\nGiven the nature of the island, they are a menace in their best state.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "After that mishap with the wolves, I must return to experimenting and trying anew. A different formula, or perhaps a new approach. \\n\\nFortunately, research is what this place was built for. What I am built for.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_02",
        "Type": "FactionStory_Syndicate",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 19,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_02_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9807_Aventus_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 17,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_02_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": null,
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Over the Cliffs, and Through the Woods",
        "Description": "Syndicate Initiation Quest: Aventus has tasked you to climb the cliffs nearby into Brightwood and east into the grove of the Azoth Tree to collect water from the moat, and then return to him.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Special and dangerous?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You're sharp! No progress comes without danger. \\n\\nTake this bottle, mind the cliffs, follow the path into Brightwood. Go through the grove, and then to the moat.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Climb over the cliffs to the northeast. We have left markers as guides for the initiates. \\n\\nIf you attract unwanted attention, I recommend you hide or run. Sometimes the quickest route is draped in shadows.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Now you've seen the Azoth Tree. It was truly beautiful, no? Well worth a little danger. \\n\\nWelcome to Aeternum, my friend. You will have infinite time to take it in.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_Vector",
        "Type": "FactionStory_Syndicate",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_Vector_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9808_Cleo_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_Vector",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 17,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_Vector_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": null,
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Woes of the Wise",
        "Description": "Syndicate Initiation Quest: Aventus has asked you to speak with Cabalist Cleo Elsayad at the Syndicate Enclave for your final initiation test.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I am willing to prove myself.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Oh, I believe you are. Go to her, and keep an open mind. \\n\\nThe task she has prepared may challenge you in more ways than one.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Go, and speak to Cleo. I eagerly await your return to the enclave.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Ah, a moment if you please. Thank you for speaking with me, Aventus has had much to say about you. \\n\\nOur order eagerly accepts capable candidates, and I hoped you would perform one final test to join our ranks. Shall we?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_03",
        "Type": "FactionStory_Syndicate",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 21,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_03_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9808_Cleo_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_Vector",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 17,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_03_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": null,
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Burden of Responsibility",
        "Description": "Syndicate Initiation Quest: Cleo has requested that you travel to Broken Hull Hold, pour the sleeping draught into their wells, disrupt their reserves, and return to her at the Syndicate Enclave.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"New problems require new solutions.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Indeed. This is an Azoth-infused sleeping draught, with which I hope to subdue our immortal foes. \\n\\nPour it into the wells at Broken Hull Hold, and destroy their reserves to force them to drink it.",
        "InProgressResponse": "It is a grim proposition, to be sure. But what should be done? \\n\\nGiven the horrific ways in which I have seen this problem approached, eternal slumber would be a blessing. We must all make difficult choices for the greater good.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You return victorious. You are truly committed to the application of knowledge, and not just its pursuit. \\n\\nDespite how you may feel about the act itself, do know that this work will help the people of Everfall.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_Recruitment",
        "Type": "FactionStory_Syndicate",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_Recruitment_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_Recruitment",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 17,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "FactionIntro_Syndicate_Recruitment_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9806_S_0001_RankUp",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": true,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "True Knowledge",
        "Description": "Syndicate Recruitment Quest: You can now join the Syndicate.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“Alright. Where do I enlist?”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Now that is some joyous news. Your letters of recommendation have already been furnished. \\n\\nGo to Scrivener Astrid and she will process your records into our charters.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Please, go to Astrid. She already has your letters of recommendation in her files.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "N/A",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": true
    }
]
